mantisadnetwork.com 2015-12-05

# Privacy Policy - MANTIS Ad Network

MANTIS Ad Network, LLC (“MANTIS”), and its wholly-owned subsidiaries (collectively MANTIS or we/us/our) respect and value your privacy. As such, this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) covers the collection and use of information from any device used to access or connect to MANTIS branded websites, services, and software, as well as many websites owned by or affiliated with MANTIS and operating under different names and explains how your information is collected, used and shared by MANTIS. MantisAdNetwork.com (“Site”) is designed for business clients and prospective business clients. The website is not directed to consumers generally.

MANTIS reserves the right to modify this Policy from time to time. Changes to the Policy will be posted on this website and the effective date of the Privacy Policy will be modified to reflect the effective date of the most recent version. If a material change to our personally identifiable information practices occurs in the future, we will only use personally identifiable information collected from the time of the policy change forward for these new purposes unless we have your consent. If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact MANTIS at [contact@MantisAdNetwork.com](mailto:contact@MantisAdNetwork.com).

## COLLECTING DATA

We collect personal information about you in various ways when you use our Site, such as when you make your information known by registering, authenticating, making purchases, or interacting through email, telephone conversations or other communications with MANTIS. If you do not make yourself known to MANTIS, your use of our content and services is generally anonymous.

The types of information we collect may include your [first and last name, physical address, billing address, email address, phone number, fax number, social security number, tax identification number, credit card information, bank account information, PayPal email address, and other contact or demographic information you choose to provide.]

MANTIS collects, in the normal course of operating its business, information that is not personally identifiable and does not reveal the specific identity of an individual and does not relate to a single identifiable visitor. We collect certain aggregate and non-personal information when you visit the Site. It tells us such things as how many users visited the Site and the pages accessed. Collecting this information helps us tailor the Site to our visitors.

Some standard computer information that your browser sends to every website you visit is automatically collected when you visit our Site, such as log information, including IP address, access times, browser type and language, access times, referring website addresses, and the website you visited before our Site. Information about your usage and activity on our Site is also recorded.

We use cookies and other technologies on our Site to collect aggregate and non-personal information. The deposit of cookies and other technologies by the Site may enhance your online experience by allowing us to save your preferences for your next visit. Our cookies may also measure the general activity on the website, which allows us to determine which areas and features are most popular. This information allows us to make improvements to our website. Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, some of the functionality of the Site may be impaired.

We may also receive information about you from other sources and combine that with information we collect through our Site.

## HOW YOUR INFORMATION IS USED

We generally use information collected through our Site for purposes described in this Policy or otherwise disclosed to you in connection with our Site. Your information is used to operate and improve our services; prevent fraudulent transactions; to fulfill your requests and to communicate with you and to provide customer service, including but not limited to, invoicing, confirmations, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages; to conduct research by monitoring and analyzing trends, usage and activities in connection with our Site; to personalize the content and advertisements provided to you; to communicate with you about new promotions and contests, upcoming events, and other news about products and services offered by MANTIS and/or our selected partners; and to link or combine with other information we get from third parties, to help understand your needs and provide you with better.

MANTIS will not sell, rent or lease personally identifiable information collected on this site to third-party marketers.

MANTIS is based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. By accessing or using the Site or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other countries.

## HOW YOUR INFORMATION IS SHARED

MANTIS may share the information collected through our Site in limited circumstances, including when we have your consent to do so or (1) when sharing is necessary to protect MANTIS in complying with any applicable law, regulation or legal process, or as otherwise required by any applicable law, rule or regulation, including but not limited to receipt of a properly authorized and authenticated governmental request for information or a subpoena or a court order; (2) with our agents and contractors who assist us with our marketing efforts and communications, such as third party vendors, consultants and other service providers who work on our behalf or with us to provide the Site, and need access to your information to carry out our operations; or, (3) if we believe your actions are inconsistent with the spirit or language of our user agreements or policies, or in an effort to safeguard the person, rights or property of a MANTIS employee or others.

We may allow other companies to provide analytics services on our behalf. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Site, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages and links clicked. This information may be used by MANTIS to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand your online activity.

In addition, MANTIS may, in the future, decide to sell, merge or otherwise reorganize its business. MANTIS reserves the right to transfer and disclose your information in this circumstance, but data collected by MANTIS will be governed by the same privacy policy that existed prior to any change in business conditions unless you consent to a new privacy policy.

## SECURITY

MANTIS endeavors to safeguard and protect your information in an effort to protect against loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction of personal information under our control. We process information in a way that is compatible with and relevant for the purpose for which it was collected. To the extent necessary for those purposes, we take reasonable steps to ensure that any information in our care is accurate, complete, current and reliable for its intended use.

Currently, MANTIS uses Secure Socket Layer Software (“SSL”) to protect data and to secure any transactions. SSL encrypts information, including credit card numbers, names and addresses as they are transmitted over the Internet. Please be advised that, although we take reasonable technological precautions to protect your data, no data transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, MANTIS cannot warrant that your information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data at or through our website is at your own risk. However, access to your information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public.

## YOU HAVE CHOICES

You can opt-out of the use of your data for interest-based advertising. For more information, please visit:  
<http://www.mantisadnetwork.com/faq/opt-tracking/>

You can manage cookies using browser controls. For more information, please visit:  
<http://www.mantisadnetwork.com/faq/disable-cookies/>

## CA PRIVACY RIGHTS

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to request from a business, with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, certain information with respect to the types of personal information the business shares with third parties for direct marketing purposes by such third party and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year.

To request a copy of the information disclosure provided by MANTIS pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, please contact [contact@MantisAdNetwork.com](mailto:contact@MantisAdNetwork.com) or by mail to:

MANTIS Ad Network, LLC  
Privacy Department  
17216 Saticoy St #616  
Van Nuys CA 91406

Upon receipt of your request, we will provide a list of the categories of personally identifiable information disclosed to third parties for third-party direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of these third parties. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the address specified in this section.

## HOW TO CONTACT US

MANTIS Ad Network, LLC  
17216 Saticoy St #616  
Van Nuys CA 91406  

Last Updated  
May 7th, 2014
